theidealmeal.com 2019-01-03

# Privacy

1\. Changes to Privacy Policy
     We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you by among other ways, posting the revised Privacy Policy in the "Privacy Policy" section of the Site. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted. It is your responsibility to review the Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any modifications. Your continued use of the Site, or any product or service offered through the Site, after the posting of any modifications will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy. 
2\. Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information

We collect two types of information about our Site Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

**Personally Identifiable Information.** Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific End User. When you engage in certain activities on or off the Website, such as creating an account, signing in to your account, ordering a product or service from us or our partners, adding items to your shopping cart, submitting content and/or posting User Content, entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, filling out a survey, posting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, requesting information about our services, submitting an affiliate agreement, applying for a job or to be a consultant or supplier, posting a video or signing up for special offers from third parties through the Website (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, telephone number, date of birth and Restaurant.com account information. When you order products or services, we may also ask you to provide us with your credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information. We may also know your location if you access the Site. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity 

We may collect, use and store Personally Identifiable Information, including credit card information, to provide products and services to you, make the log-in and checkout process easier, administer our Rewards Program, sweepstakes and contests, help you track your past purchases and orders, enhance the operation of the Site, improve our marketing and promotional efforts to your tastes and location, customize future shopping interests, analyze Site use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with third parties as provided in Item 3 of this Privacy Policy. 

If you provide User Content, such as an email to our customer service or response to a restaurant survey, we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. In connection with such User Content and our Rewards Program, we may also display partial information such as first name, initial of last name, city and state. Such partial information is not considered Personally Identifiable Information. 

In addition, if you use our Site to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of any recipient. We may use that other person’s contact information to allow him or her to view and accept your gift or to allow the recipient to access the information you requested we send. As another example, if you put items in your shopping cart, we may save the items you have selected to make your checkout process easier in the future, or to remind you about the items you may have forgotten. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific End User. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described in Items 4 and 8 of this Privacy Policy. 

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming.. 

back to top
3\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below: 

**We may share your information with Affiliated Restaurants.** We provide some products or services jointly with particular restaurants. These are known as "Affiliated Restaurants." We share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliated Restaurants in order to help them provide you with better service and track the value of our program. Sharing this Information will allow an Affiliated Restaurant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with an Affiliated Restaurant if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the Affiliated Restaurant involved in that Identification Activity. For example, if you purchase a promotional certificate for a particular restaurant, we may share your name, email address and city with that restaurant. We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information with an Affiliated Restaurant if you choose to make an online reservation using our Website. The Affiliated Restaurant needs this information to complete the reservation and it may contact you regarding the reservation. 

**We may share your information with Affiliated Businesses.** We provide some products or services jointly with other retail merchants who offer goods or services through us and donation opportunities through charitable organizations. These are known as "Affiliated Businesses." We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with an Affiliated Business so they can contact you regarding a transaction. Sharing this Information will allow an Affiliated Business to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with an Affiliated Business if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the Affiliated Business involved in that Identification Activity. For example, if you purchase a promotional certificate or voucher for a particular retail merchant, we may share your name, email address and city with that merchant. 

**We may share your information with Marketing Partners.** From time to time we may establish a business relationship with third parties. These are known as our "Marketing Partners." We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our Marketing Partners to enable them to contact you regarding products, services, and special offers that may be of interest to you. Some Marketing Partners may contact you from a promotional space on our Website, and others may contact you via email. 

**We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** We provide some of our services and products through third parties. These "Third Party Service Providers" perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer our Rewards Program contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information and improve information on customer lists and databases, analyze data and activities, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies ("Affiliates") with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a service, we release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the service and, if applicable, release your address to the delivery service to deliver the service. Likewise, we may release an Affiliate’s information to our bank to send out a payment. 

We encourage Affiliated Restaurants, Affiliated Businesses, Marketing Partners and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. 

**We may share your information in a Business Transfer.** As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others. 

back to top
4\. Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with "Third Party Advertisers" or "Third Party Advertising Companies" and other parties as provided below: 

We use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Some of these Third Party Advertising Companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). If you would like more information about any NAI member company, or you would like to opt-out of targeted advertising from any NAI member company, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

We also use Third Party Service Providers, like Adobe, to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us. If you would like more information about this policy, including how to opt out, please visit: [ http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html ](http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html)

5\. Updating and Correcting Information

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by: (1) updating your account at  https://www.restaurant.com/account/myprofile  (2) [ emailing us ](mailto:info@restaurant.com); or (3) writing to us at the address below. Please indicate your name, address and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us. 

We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Website. In addition in may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information because we periodically backup information. 

6\. User Choices on Collection and Use of Information

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website. 

As a condition of account registration, we require your permission to send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User’s activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User’s account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails update you about new services available on our Site, and advertise our products and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, our Rewards Program and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. We send Promotional Emails to Users who register with us and have not opted-out of receiving Promotional Emails. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by (1) adjusting your account preferences at [ http://www.restaurant.com/my-restaurant.asp; ](https://www2.restaurant.com/accountmanager/account/login/) (2) [ emailing us ](mailto:info@restaurant.com); (3) writing to us at the address found below, or (4) hitting the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of any of our promotional emails.When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Promotional Emails you do not want to receive. For SMS Text Messaging, reply “Stop” and we will remove you from receiving SMS Text Alerts. Please note that this paragraph applies to Promotional Emails only if another agreement (like an Incentive or Loyalty Solution ("ILS") Division agreement or Affiliate agreement) does not supersede this term of the policy. If you received a promotional certificate through our ILS division, please either [contact us](mailto:corpsalesinfo@restaurant.com) or contact the company that gave you the certificate to determine if our Promotional Email Policy applies to you. 

You also have a choice with respect to the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliated Businesses and Marketing Partners for direct marketing purposes (but not with Affiliated Businesses for transaction-related purposes, Affiliated Restaurants, or Third Party Service Providers). As described above, if we share your Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliated Business or Marketing Partners, such companies may contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners for direct marketing purposes, you may elect to opt-out of such information sharing after you sign up as a registered User by (1) adjusting your account preferences at [ http://www.restaurant.com/my-restaurant.asp; ](https://www2.restaurant.com/accountmanager/account/login/) (2) [ emailing us ](mailto:info@restaurant.com); or (3) writing to us at the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what information you do not want us to share with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners. Please note that because email addresses and names are one mechanism used by Affiliated Restaurants to track the success of our service, we must share your name and address with an Affiliated Restaurant when you purchase or redeem a promotional certificate to that particular Affiliated Restaurant. If you receive unwanted communication from an Affiliated Restaurant, contact such Affiliated Restaurant directly to address such communications. 

Please note that opting out of our Promotional Emails or information sharing as described above will only affect future communications from us. This means, for example, that while we will promptly stop sharing such information once we receive your opt-out request, if we shared your information with an Affiliated Business or Marketing Partner before your request, you must contact such Marketing Partner or Affiliated Business to directly opt-out of its communications. 

If you are a restaurant, merchant or other business partner, including a charitable organization and you provided us with your email address, you will receive service-oriented Partner Emails from us regarding your account. You have the choice of whether you would like to receive these emails. If you do not wish to receive account updates, you can opt-out by (1) [ emailing us ](mailto:partnersupport@restaurant.com); (2) writing to us at the address found below; or (3) hitting the unsubscribe button at the bottom of an account email. If you wish not to receive our customer promotional emails, you must opt-in to those emails on our consumer Website. Please note that opting-out (once you have opted-in) of Promotional Emails will not result in your opting out of Partner Emails and vice versa. 

back to top
7\. Security of Information

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and unique User ID selected by you, or, for restaurant partners, by us. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information. 

8\. Data Tracking

**Cookies.** To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User’s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies and other browser analytics tools to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, administer our Rewards Program and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies and web analytics tools also allow us to collect information about your experience, like which pages you visited, what links you clicked on, and, when combined with information you provide to us, we may be able to tell what kind of items you may be interested in to make your experience more enjoyable. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly. 

**Other Tracking Devices.** We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags, web beacons and other tools to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. These tools are software code that allows us to determine what pages you visit, whether you have performed a specific action, etc. When you access these pages or open or click an email, these tools generate a notice of that action. These tools allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags, web beacons and other tools provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes. 

9\. Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites
     This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you review the website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. 
10\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

**Children.** Minors under the age of 13 may not use the Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 13, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13. 

**Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.** California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the "Act") and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the Act, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Website and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. We do not enable third parties to collect Personally Identifiable Information from the use of our Website for their own purposes (except through an Identification Activity) whether over time, across third party websites, or other online services. We do not respond to associated "do not track" mechanisms. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. The Act further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or standard mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice. 

**Notice to Residents Outside the United States.** We are based in the United States and you acknowledge that the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. You are solely responsible for compliance with any protection or privacy obligation in your jurisdiction when you use the Site or provide us with information. Our operations are supported by a network of computers, cloud-based servers, and other infrastructure and information technology, including, but not limited to, Third Party Service Providers. By accessing or using our Site or services, or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer and storage of information in and to the United States, and elsewhere around the world where we (or our Third Party Service Providers) may access the information. Please note that the locations which may process, transfer, or store information may have privacy and data protection laws that differ from your local jurisdiction, and those locations may not provide the same rights and protections as you do under your local laws. Regardless, we will protect your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

11\. Contacting Us

Whether you’re a new or loyal customer, restaurant owner, marketer, publisher, media member or job seeker we’d like to stay connected and want to hear from you! 

Corporate Address
     Restaurant.com  
1500 West Shure Drive, Suite 600  
Arlington Heights, Illinois 60004 
Phone

For Customers:  
1-800-979-8985 Toll-free  
(8:30a.m. - 5:00p.m. CST, Monday through Friday) 

For Restaurants:  
1-877-640-1844   __Toll-free  
(9:00a.m. - 5:00p.m. CST, Monday through Friday) 

Email

Customer Service Inquiries | [info@restaurant.com](mailto:info@restaurant.com)

Restaurant Owner Inquiries from Prospective Partners | [partnerjoin@restaurant.com](mailto:partnerjoin@restaurant.com)

Corporate Business Inquiries | [corpsalesinfo@restaurant.com](mailto:corpsalesinfo@restaurant.com)

Marketing and Advertising Opportunities | [marketing@restaurant.com](mailto:marketing@restaurant.com)

Press and Media Requests | [pr@restaurant.com](mailto:pr@restaurant.com)

Career Opportunities | [jobs@restaurant.com](mailto:jobs@restaurant.com)
